

## **CONTACT ME**

- Sri Lanka
- ✓ shehan.abeyrathne96@gmail.com
- **\** +94 76 04 121 30
- in linkedin.com/in/shehanabeyrathne-58b262152

## **SKILLS SUMMARY**

- Front End: Angular 8+, React JS, Redux, HTML, CSS, JS, Material Design
- Back End : Node JS
- Mobile App : Android (Kotlin), iOS (Swift), Ionic
- CMS: Wordpress
- DevOps: Github, Docker, Kubernetes
- Infrastructure:
   Digitalocean, AWS, Google
   Cloud
- Database: Mysql, Firebase, MongoDB

## **EDUCATION**

Bsc. (Hons) in Software Engineering - NSBM | 2015-2019 Second Upper Class - GPA 3.69

### AWARDS

 Champions - NSBBM Mini Hackaton

## **VOLUNTERR WORK**

- Member FOSS NSBM
- Team Leader NSAC

# SHEHAN ABEYRATHNE

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER

### PERSONAL PROFILE

A competent full stack developer with 4+ years of handson experience in design, development, testing, and managing highly scalable web-based and mobile-based software products. Possesses experience in database management, UI designing, API designing, infrastructure managing seeking a full stack developer opportunity.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Adelmo Technology | October 2018 - Present

- Customer requirement gathering and SRS document creating.
- Meeting both technical and consumer needs.
- Developing system architecture.
- Frontend UI&UX designing.
- Backend development.
- Designing and developing API's.
- Integrating 3rd party API's.
- Database development.
- Deploying web applications.
- Configure cloud servers
- Maintaning sure code in Github.
- Maintaining, upgrading, and continuously patching resources in test and production environments.
- Setting up new environments based on the developer team requirements.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TRAINEE

KPMG Technology Solutions | July 2018 - September 2018

- Developing mobile apps using android & ionic.
- Developing admin panels using angular framework
- Developing RestAPIs using java spring boot.

#### **INTERNSHIP**

Imperium (Pvt) LTD | February 2018 - July 2018

- Developing websites using HTML,CSS & JS.
- Developing websites using Wordpress.
- Developing e-commerce websites using Wordpress and Woo-commerce plugin.